Sign Up

Sign up

Already have an account?

Sign in

Privacy Policy

Updated April 1, 2024

=======================================

Z League Inc. ("Z League", "us", "we", or "our") operates the website www.zleague.gg (the "Website"), the skill-based tournament platform available through our Website and mobile application available on iOS and Android (the "App") (together, the "Services"). This Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how Z League collects, uses, and discloses your personal data when using our Services, and to help you understand and exercise your privacy rights. By using the Services, you agree to the collection and use of information in accordance with this policy. If you object to the practices described in this policy, you should (a) remove cookies from your computer after leaving our Website, and (b) discontinue your use of our Services. This Privacy Policy is incorporated by reference into our [Terms of Use](https://www.zleague.gg/terms).

If you are an individual located in the European Economic Area, the UK, or Switzerland, the GDPR Privacy Notice available here applies to you.

Personal Information We Collect

The categories of personal information we collect depend on how you interact with us, our Services, and the requirements of applicable law. For example, we may collect different information from you depending on whether you are a visitor to our Website or register to use our Services as a player, or whether you seek to claim a tournament prize that you have won. We primarily collect information that you provide to us or that we obtain automatically when you use our Services.

1. Information you provide to us directly
    
    We may collect the following personal information that you provide to us:
    
    1. When you register for and use the Services. When you register for the Services, we typically collect fields such as your first name, last name, gamertag (or similar gamer ID), email address, state/province, country, and birthdate.
        
    2. Your communications with us. We may collect your name, email address, postal address, and telephone number when you request information about our Services, request customer or technical support, or otherwise communicate with us.
        
    3. Surveys/Questionnaires. We may contact you to participate in surveys or other questionnaires following a tournament to collect feedback. If you decide to participate, you may be asked to provide certain information, which may include personal information.
        
2. Information we collect automatically
    
    We also automatically collect certain information based on your use of our Services. This data would include your activities on our Website and App. For example, we, or our third-party partners, may collect:
    
    1. Details of the activities you carry out when using our Services, including real-time geographic location from which the transaction originates;
        
    2. Technical information, including the Internet protocol (IP) address used to connect your computer to the internet, your login information, browser type and version, time zone setting, browser plug-in types and versions, operating system, and platform;
        
    3. Information about your visit to our Website, including clickstream data, through and from our Website (including date and time), page response times, errors, device metadata, length of visits to certain pages, page interaction information, referral and exiting URLs; and
        
    4. Information about your mobile device, internet connection, including the device's unique device identifier, IP address, operating system, browser type, mobile network information, and users’ contact list information including but not limited to phone numbers, names, emails, and other such information included in the users’ contact list.

    For more information regarding use of "tracking technologies" and related collection of information, please see the Cookies section below.
    
3. Information we obtain from service providers and third parties
    
    When you seek to claim a tournament prize, you will be required to verify your identity through Persona, one of our Service Providers (as such term is defined below). Persona may ask you to provide a photograph of yourself, government-issued identifiers, or biometric data, in order to confirm you are in fact who you are claiming to be. This is one way we aim to keep our tournaments fair for all players.

How we use your Information

When you sign up to use our Services, you enter into a contract with us to make available our tournaments to you, and, for winners of such tournaments, certain prizes. We must process your data to fulfil this contract. Further, we are required by law to collect, process, and retain your data, in fulfilment of our anti-money laundering regulatory obligations and under state and federal laws governing unlawful gambling. We use your data for the following business purposes:

1. Provide, monitor, maintain, personalize, optimize, and improve the Services, including research and analytics regarding use of the Services, or to remember you when you leave and return to the Services;
    
2. Notify you about changes to our Services;
    
3. Provide you with news, special offers, and general information about other goods, services, and events which we offer that are similar to those that you have already purchased or inquired about, unless you have opted not to receive such information;
    
4. Allow you to participate in interactive features within our Services when you choose to do so;
    
5. Provide you with customer support;
    
6. Carry out our obligations relating to your contracts with us and to provide you with the information and Services that you request from us;
    
7. Provide you or other users on your contact list with more relevant content in marketing, promotional, or other communications to which you may be subscribed; and
    
8. Detect, investigate, and prevent technical issues, or activities that may violate our policies or be fraudulent or illegal.

We may combine information from the Services together and with other information we obtain from our business records or from third party sources.

We are required by law to store some of your data beyond the termination of your relationship with us. After such time, your data will only be accessed or processed as necessary.

How we disclose your information

Z League may share data to ensure that we can continue providing you with the Services you have contracted. We may share certain information with:

1. Service providers.
    
    We share data with service providers who help us provide the Services (each, a "Service Provider"). Service Providers help us with things like payment processing, Website hosting, data analysis, information technology and related infrastructure, identity verification, customer service, and email delivery. For example, we occasionally provide paid products or services through the Services. When we do, we use third-party payment processors to effectuate your purchase, such as PayPal. We share your payment card details with our third party payment processors and the handling of your personal information is governed by their respective privacy practices.
    
2. Third parties authorized by you.
    
    We share data with parties directly authorized by a customer to receive data. The use of data by an authorized third party is subject to the third party’s privacy policy and any agreements the customer has with the third party.
    
3. Successors-in-interest.
    
    We will share data with third parties in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer, or other disposition of all or any portion of our business, assets, or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings) and, in each case, any due diligence relating thereto; and
    
4. Safety, legal purposes, and law enforcement.
    
    We use and disclose data as we believe necessary: (i) under applicable law; (ii) to enforce our terms and conditions; (iii) to protect our rights, privacy, safety, or property, or the safety or property of yours or others; and (iv) to respond to requests from courts, law enforcement agencies, regulatory agencies, and other public and government authorities, which may include authorities outside your country of residence.
    
5. Advertising platforms.
    
    We may share certain information with advertising platforms, such as Google and Facebook, to select and serve relevant adverts to you and others. The information shared may include device-level information and analytics, as discussed in detail in "Information we collect automatically," or email addresses.

    We use a third-party to provide monetization technologies for our site. You can review their privacy and cookie policy [here](https://www.snigel.com/privacy-policy/).
    
6. Analytics and search engine providers.
    
    We may share certain information with analytics and search engine providers that assist us in the improvement and optimization of our site.

Any information, including personal information, you disclose in a post or chat may be publically available and you should exercise caution in deciding whether to include any personal, financial or other sensitive information in any post or chat.

Transfers outside the U.S.

Personal information that we collect may be transferred to, and stored and processed in, the United States or any other country in which we or our subcontractors or partner payment processors maintain facilities. The laws in the U.S. and other countries regarding personal information may be different from the laws of your state or country. To the extent permitted by applicable law, by submitting your personal data to us, you agree to this transfer, storing, or processing.

Our policy on "Do Not Track" signals

We do not support Do Not Track ("DNT") requests. Do Not Track is a preference you can set in your web browser to inform websites that you do not want to be tracked. You can enable or disable Do Not Track by visiting the Preferences or Settings page of your web browser.

Service Providers and Third Parties

Our Service may, from time to time, contain links to other websites, mobile applications, or digital properties that are not operated by us, including those of our Service Providers, which you may access either directly, via an authentication process, or otherwise through the Services. Likewise, other websites, mobile applications, or digital properties may reference or link to our Services. These third-party services are not controlled by us and we do not have any responsibility over their privacy and security practices. We encourage our players to read the privacy policies and terms of service of each website and application with which they interact. We also strongly advise that you review the privacy policy and terms of use of each of our Service Providers prior to engaging with our Services (see Annex A).

We do not endorse, screen, or approve, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices or content of such other websites, mobile applications, or digital properties. Providing personal information to them, both within or outside of our Website or our Services, is at your own risk.

Children's Privacy

Our Services are not intended for children under the age of 13. We do not knowingly collect personal information from children under the age of 13. If you are a parent or guardian and you believe that your child under the age of 13 has provided us with their information, please contact us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.zleague.gg/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection). If we become aware that a child has provided us with personal information in violation of applicable law, we will delete any personal information we have collected, unless we have a legal obligation to keep it.

Cookies

We use cookies and similar tracking technologies to track activity on our Services. Cookies are files with a small amount of data, which may include a pseudonymous unique identifier. Cookies are sent to your browser from a website and stored on your device. Other tracking technologies are also used such as beacons, tags, and scripts to collect and track information and to improve and analyze our Services.

You can instruct your browser to refuse all cookies or to inform you when a cookie is being sent. However, if you do not accept cookies from us, you may not be able to use certain of our Services.

Google and Facebook Advertising. To the extent we use Google or Facebook for advertising purposes on our Website, please see these links provided by these respective companies for opt-out purposes: [Google](https://support.google.com/accounts/answer/2662856)/[Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/help/568137493302217). We are not responsible regarding the scope of, or the honoring of, any such opt-outs, as opt-out preferences provided by these companies are not under our control.

Further, you may stop or restrict the placement of third-party cookie technologies on your device or remove them by adjusting your preferences as your browser or device permits. However, please note that cookie-based opt-outs are typically not effective on mobile applications. You may opt-out of personalized advertisements on some mobile applications by following the instructions for [Android](https://support.google.com/googleplay/android-developer/answer/6048248?hl=en), [iOS](https://support.apple.com/en-us/HT202074) and [others](https://www.networkadvertising.org/mobile-choice/).

More broadly, the online advertising industry also provides websites from which you may opt out of receiving targeted ads from data partners and other advertising partners that participate in self-regulatory programs. You can access these and learn more about targeted advertising and consumer choice and privacy by visiting the [Network Advertising Initiative](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp), the [Digital Advertising Alliance](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/), the [European Digital Advertising Alliance](https://www.youronlinechoices.eu/), and the [Digital Advertising Alliance of Canada](https://youradchoices.ca/choices/). Please note you must separately opt out in each browser and on each device.

Marketing communications

You have the right to ask us not to contact you for marketing purposes by following the unsubscribe link or the instructions provided in any email we send, or by contacting us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.zleague.gg/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Security of your information

We take steps to ensure that your information is treated securely and in accordance with this Privacy Policy. Unfortunately, no method of transmission over the internet or method of electronic storage is 100% secure. We take reasonable measures to help protect information about you from loss, theft, misuse and unauthorized access, disclosure, alteration, and destruction.

You are responsible for keeping confidential any passwords you use to access our Services. We ask you not to share this password with anyone else and not to use this password for other services or products.

To the fullest extent permitted by applicable law, we do not accept liability for any unauthorized disclosure.

Changes to this Privacy Policy

We may update our Privacy Policy from time to time. Any changes we may make to our Privacy Policy will be posted on this page and, where appropriate, notified to you by e-mail or in your Z League account. The date the Privacy Policy was last revised is identified at the top of the page. You are responsible for periodically visiting our Website and this Privacy Policy to check for any changes.

Contact Us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please email us at [\[email protected\]](https://www.zleague.gg/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection).

Annex A

1. PayPal
    
    * Legal Agreements for PayPal Services are available [here](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/legalhub-full).
        
2. Persona
